Thank you for watching!
Hi, I'm Sanauit.
So, um, it's a little bit Ebidan's Live,
I've brought a little something for the Ebbidan's Live.
It's a cheesecake made from saramushi.
I'd like to give it to all the EBIDAN members to eat.
What's that?
Wow, it looks good!
Well, it looks good, doesn't it?
Oh, it looks delicious!
Yes, I've brought it here, chilled and ready to eat,
I ate it yesterday, so you don't have to worry about getting a stomach ache.
No, I don't know.
I'd like you to try it first.
It's a poisoned taste.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
I'm going to eat.
Ah! What?
Wow!
What? That's so good!
What the...?
I'm not even thinking about Mariakushon anymore, am I?
You should be like, "Which one of these guys should we go with?
Wait, what?
What?
There's paper in it.
No, no, no.
It's like cooking paper.
I couldn't get it off.I couldn't get it off.
AVAMOU.
There's nothing I can't take.
Oh, man.
You should keep this one to yourself.
everyone else, get in the family!
I'm leaving again!
Hey, Nana.
It seems it's still out there.
It's paper!
It's already paper!
Eat that, too. Paper.
I don't want it.
Bon appétit.
It's good.
Is it good?
It doesn't taste good.
It's not?
It's...
It's like a flavorless version of pudding.
Oh, yeah.
I told you not to put a lot of cheese and stuff in there, in my comment.
No, I put a lot of cheese in it.
Can you eat it? It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's not great, but it's...
It's edible.
Oh, it would be really good with strawberry jam or something.
Oh, it's not sweet.
No, but I'm sure there's some maple syrup or something.
Oh...Uh...
I think it's that kind of thing, right?
It's edible.
No, no, no, no, no, don't eat that.
I can't help it.
It's hard to get a reaction out of him.
Oh, yeah.
They served this to me.
You might want to add this to the list now.
No, on the other hand, if you can get a good reaction out of the shrimp gang...
I'll be a Malaibi.
That's for sure.
That's what we're doing this time.
Um...
I wonder how they would react if they were served a cheesecake that was neither good nor bad.
I wonder how they would react.
It would be funny if I said it was good.
It's not good.
Let's go.
Enjoy it.
I'm off.
Eat well.
Who's with me?
Yankees!
Tanaka, wake up!
Yankee gang.
Good morning.
I slept like a baby.
Sorry, sorry, Coki.
I'm Ki-no-chiku-ta-mame-shina...This is Kinoshiku-tamashimashimashina here.
Wow!
It looks so delicious!
I'd like you to try it and tell me what you think.
I'm sorry, that's what this project is about.
It looks like cheesecake.
Looks like cheesecake.
Looks hard.
Like this.
Here you go.
Delicious!
Here you go
Here, here
Hoi, hoi, hoi
Oh, Mr. Jang ate it.
I don't know about that.
I'll put you with the wrappers.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, it's good.
It's delicious.
Like this?
What?
I was kind of expecting it.
It's not biting.
How much do you eat?
It's low in sugar.
It's low in sugar. That's for sure.
It's easy to eat.
Kaiichi!Mr. Kaiti.
I'd like to make a proper comment.
You're the best.
Subachi has never eaten cheesecake before!
Mmmm!
Hey!
What!
What's wrong with you, eating that?
It's delicious.
It's just so smooth.
And, um...
I like ice cream.
I like ice cream, so I thought, "Wow, this is really good.
I thought it was good.
I was waiting for a comment that it was bad.
I was waiting for a comment that it's not good, but when you say it's good...
What the hell is this?
If you can eat it
It's real.
It's so rare.
Do you want to take a picture of that version?
The bad version.
Can I have a picture of the bad version?
No, no, no.
Bad version.
Can I get a first reaction?
No, but I don't think we have it.
Not in the store?
Not in the store.
You're right, you're right, you're right.Sure, sure.
But what do you think?
I'm the oldest.
Hmm?
But I think it's delicious with a hint of cheese.
Oh, wow.
What's that?
It would taste amazing with a sweet milk tea or something.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's got a certain sweetness to it.
He's saying something, he's saying something.
What?
It's got a little bit of a kick to it.
I don't think so.
What?
It tastes like...
Taste?
No, I know what it tastes like.
I totally get it.
It's not bad.
Try it.
Mmm.
Why can't you make it worse?
No, it was bad yesterday when I ate it.
What?
And by the way, they're probably all chewing on it, like normal.
The kitchen.
Ehhhh...
Ehhhh...Ehhhh...
Huh?
Oh, really? Don't bite?
I say it all the time.
What's not to bite?
Raku, Raku is strict.
Raku is strict.
He's strict.
He's a good cook.
How about you, Raku?
Delicious.
Hey...
What's the matter?
I don't know...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what you're saying.
What are you saying?
Ha-ha-ha.
What about you, Mr. Raku?
You know what I'm saying?
What's this?
Cheesecake.
It's another cheesecake.
Oh?
Aah!
Be honest with me.
Honestly?
Honestly, please.Honest Please
No, I'm not.
Oh!
here it comes!
ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
A-ha-ha-ha
I'm done
I'm done.
I'm done!
But it's like an egg tart.
It's just plain delicious.
I don't know.
I know what you mean.
It's like a hard pudding.
Not too sweet and not too sweet and not too sweet and not too sweet and not too sweet and not too sweet.
It's not cheesecake.
But it's still that.
Mr. Sano.
You should know your followers.
You should know who your followers are.
For someone with a million followers...
Uh...
No.
No, no, no, no.
No. No.
no.
How many of you enjoyed it?
Uh, one of them was good.Oh, one was delicious.
Yum! Yum!
Yummy.
It's not that it's good.
More like delicious.
Thank you very much.
What?
Cheesecake.
I love it.
Oh, you must eat it.
I won't eat it.
It's cloudy.
What? It's cloudy.
And it's not cloudy.
Hmm.
It's the in-camera.
Oh, wow.
Bon appétit!
Oh, but...
I've never made a creative cheesecake.
I've never made a mistake.
Let's eat.
Let's eat this!
Eat, eat, eat, eat.
Eat it! Eat it!
Can we eat all of this?
What?
Hey, guys...
That's a lot of food.It's a little too much.
A little less.
A little.
It's so good!
Eat it all!
Eat, eat, eat!
Eat, eat, eat.
Don't eat all of it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's a lot of food.
That's too much food.
Aloha.
You're making noise.
Excuse me.
By the way...
There's some kind of honey on your throat.
It's like honey on your throat.
Oh, that's right.
Yum!
Oh, so that's what it is.
Is it good?
It's some kind of Chinese honey.
It's got, like...
There's crab in it.
That's kitchen paper.
Hey!
What's that thing on top?
What's on the top?The one above is that
It's honey for your throat.
I thought maybe people would sing it.
Oh, yum!
There are only two vocalists here.
It's like honey for your throat
We're all dancers here
I'm counting on you, Haruharu.
You're the only one junior here, so you're mine.
That's fine.
Are you serious?
Squid!
You all use the keys.
You're telling me it's good.
It's really good, but...
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Thank you very much.
You really made it, didn't you?
I'm serious about this.
I made them yesterday.
But you know what?
I really wouldn't buy it.
Thank you for your time.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.Hello.
I'm Aito Sano.
Well, I've made Sano rice.
Um...
Um, please eat this and give me your feedback!
I'm so happy!
What do you think of this?
Well, I'd like you to try it and guess what it is.
I'll take a guess.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so good!
Gacchi?
What is this?
Cake? Cheesecake?
Cheesecake. Cheesecake, actually.
Oh, you know, it's good if you're taking your meds.
You, you, you...
Everyone laughed.
Are you kidding me?
Are you okay?
It doesn't taste good?
No, it's delicious.
What?
When did you eat it?
Uh, last night.
Really?
It's good.
It's really good.
It's insanely good.It's insanely good!
Oh, that was the best cheesecake I've ever had!
You're lying for sure!
Everyone burst out laughing!
You look like a liar.
What do you think?
Pudding?
It's not pudding.
It's a cake.
It's cheesecake.
Everyone laughed.
What's good and what's not?
Partially.
It's all mixed up.
You probably ate that in Sweden, didn't you?
No, they ate a lot of paper.
Cocking paper.
Did you eat paper? I did.
It looks so good!
Everyone laughed
Bon appétit!
I'm afraid you don't know what you're doing.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit!
Bon appétit!
machines risky multifunction?
You scared me.
Oh, my God.
This is fun.
It was.
I don't know.
We can connect here.
Insta.
Sta tuna
is the
object
and
Obje...
I'm gonna be...
That's awesome.
Because...
No cup.
Yeah.
Six Kyomoto kan.Kyomoto Kan is one of the six
In order
All the way to the good part.
Oh, well, that's for sure.
What about Matsukura?
My part is not so good.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's good!
Seriously?
You can't do that!
What did you make, Nakamura?
Cheesecake
Huh?
Wasn't that him?
They just came.
Oh, you made it, Kaito?
Oh, I made it.
Bon appétit!
I didn't look at the recipe yesterday.
It doesn't taste good.
What?
Ha-ha-ha.
It doesn't taste good!
No, it doesn't taste good!
Now it's going to be good for everyone!
I was just saying it tastes good in Manjuu 1.
I think it might be dangerous.
No, I don't know about that.
You're in my way, you're in my way, you're in my way.
Hey! Hey, wait!Hey! Wait a minute!
I'm starting to lose confidence.
I don't know if I'm any good at this.
Which way?
You know what? I had to start over. I said it was good.
It was good.
Why did you say it didn't taste good?
Why do you say it's bad now?
Is it because of the variety?
That's...
It's fine.
Jam said it was a bad idea.
It's over.
That's what I meant.
That's how it happened.
It's really good.
They're eating so much.
You're not gonna eat it?
Oh, here you go, here you go.
That was delicious.
I mean, it flowed like a delicious stream.
It was so good.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me for interrupting.Sorry to interrupt.
Let me spin a little milk YouTube for you.
Oh, there it is!
It's the one from InstaLive.
It's the one! The head chef did the ergan!
He's the head chef, right?
He's laughing his heart out.
Mizuki's trying to compete with Samamushi.
Oh, yeah.
What's his name?
You don't have to say.
Then we'll all eat together, and then Mizuki will eat last.
That's right.
How is it?
The texture is really good.
It's so moist.
I see.
Like a cheesecake.
Cheesecake?
I had some.
It's called cheesecake.
Is it good?
No, it's good.
But it's kind of like cheesecake.
What? Is it good?
It's good.It's good.
But it's not cheesecake.
What?
What do you think?
It's like apricot pudding.
Apricot jelly?
It's so apricot bean curd.
This?
May I have some?
Yes, please.
This is cheesecake, right?
Apricot curd.
By definition.
Apricot curd?
Yes, indeed.
But... it's so smooth in the mouth.
The cheesecake remains dry in the mouth.
It's very thin in the mouth.
You have to move the wind a lot.
If the eyes are smoother...
When you smile, it's a little bit slippery.
It's got a lot of power.
The crunchiness comes in.
It's smooth and it's firm.
That's what's so good about it.
This cheesecake.
It's the last one.
Rust.Rust.
You were so helpful!
Thank you so much.
Laughter
Thank you very much.
Just in case you've only had a growth party.
Laughter
Scary!
Iwamoto-san, my stomach hurts.
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am.
Good morning.
Everyone's reading each other.
Wow!
I made cheesecake yesterday.
You know...
The one with the egg whites in it.
LOL!
Wait a minute.
There's an audience out there.
Even the egg whites.
I thought you were the only one.
I'm watching so much.
That's why I'm jumping up and down at the mention of cheesecake.
He's a little jumpy.
Heh.
We're reading each other.There's a reading.
We read each other
We're going to read each other.
I'm the first one to hit you, aren't I?
I'll say it.
Like this.
The youngest.
Youngest.
We have to read each other.
I'm gonna be honest with you. It's not gonna work.
I changed it a while ago, and...
It shows a little bit.
Ah!
It's got a really delicious aftertaste.
I mean, it's really delicious.
My nose is a little stuffy right now.
Wait a minute.
I couldn't taste it at first.
But when you eat it, it has a delicious aftertaste.
You mean the smell that goes up your nose?
You've got a stuffy nose.
That's what I'm talking about, Mr. Zinke.
I'm not talking much.
I just had it... 28 bloody times...
Don't say that!
I don't know if it's that cheesecake.
It just tastes familiar.
What?
Okay, Kaname... last one.Okay, Kaname, let's make it last.
Oh, I like you then.
Wow.
Wow, that's pretty good.
It's good.
Oh, it's good?
Mm-hmm.
Mellow.
Sweet.
Okay, one last thing.
Normal.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to the next one with you.
Watch
Hello, mushrooms.
What?
I'm sorry.
I asked you to do me a favor.
Oh, you don't mind?
Bon appétit.
Oh, my God, you made this.
Oh, my God.
I didn't bite.
Don't you say that.
Oh!
That's delicious.
It really is.
I ate it.
I don't know why all these fans are saying it's not good.They said it was bad, and their fans commented
Don't make me eat that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do you rate it?
I like it a lot.
You like it a lot?
Not too sweet?
It's not too sweet?
Seriously?
I love it. I love it.
Thank you.
Zo!
Come on, man.
Das, come on, man.
Definitely you in the end.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
We're doing an Insta-movie here.
Yeah.
I made this cheesecake yesterday.
I made some cheesecake yesterday.
I'm sorry, there's only one left.
Congratulations!
Have some.
Are you sure you don't mind?
Yes, I'm sure.
Oh! How's it going?
How's it?
It's so good.It's insanely delicious.
Wait a minute.
I'm telling you how I really feel.
Eat it.
It's so good.
Really?
Did you say your name?
Kondo Shinta.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Shuto Haga.
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
What? It's delicious!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's so good!
Here's the sauce I put on it
Yes, sir.
The sauce I put on it
No, this is really delicious!
The texture
The texture...
What?
What? That one?
This is very good.
This is good.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Here you go.
Miro.
Thank you, Miro.
How's it going?How is it?
I have to admit, it's delicious.
It's really good.
Who's that? What's your name?
Wataru.
Bon appétit.
Can I have another one?
If you eat too much, you'll just drink the ice cream.
It's really good.
Thank you.
I'm going to Mr. Takagawa.
Service.
No, no, no. I'm eating.
How is it?
Wait... this is good, too.
It's delicious.
What? They're making us do it.
It fits.
It's delicious.
I'll be next.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Six?
Last one's ice cream.
There you go.
Eat this.
I'll take a variety of comments.
I'll take it.
Ice cream because...
We had it once in our milk bag.
Maybe it's the variety.Maybe he's a variety artist.
I'm sure that's true.
It's Sakuma's fault.
Yes, ma'am.
How is it?
It's good.
What's your name?
Yagami.
Yes?
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
You're so cute.
Bon appétit!
I'm Ryuya Yamamoto.
Bon appétit.
Oh...
It doesn't taste... too much.
Can you ask a question?
Ah! The perks!
Something sweet.
It's heavy!
It's something soft and sweet and delicious.
Delicious.
Let's win!
It's right!
Let's hope so!
Be honest... but tell me how you feel.
You can be honest with me.
I can't eat cheesecake.I can't eat cheesecake.
Ironing.
What are you doing?
I tasted Mr. Inokari's love.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Mr. Inokari...
I thought of your comment and a little bit
Bon appétit!
I saw it yesterday.
The first one yesterday.
I wanted to eat it.
You said you wanted to eat it yesterday.
I did.
Bon appétit.
I'm scared.
Mine.
nakata
CAMERAS
-Mine nakata cameras
Maybe.
Certification
Invisible
Dell
So, tomorrow the Ebi-dan and....
It's the show, but it's time to get going.
Tomorrow, I'm going to be the one with the most prominent feeling.
I'm going to ask you to lead the shrimp group.
I'm going to ask you to lead the Ebi-dan.
What are you talking about?What are you talking about?
With the feeling of leading the shrimp group.
I hope you'll do your best.
Well, I can only be as good as the difference in rice.
I'm only as good as my rice.
Good night!
I'm the player of the group.
Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
Thanks a lot!